ivisa.com 2019-12-17

# Our Privacy Terms in iVisa

**This Privacy Policy was last updated on July 24th, 2018**

  * Our Policy
  * Information We Collect
  * Our Use of Your Personal Data and Other Information
  * Our Disclosure of Your Personal Data and Other Information
  * Your Choices
  * Online Advertising We Use
  * Exclusions
  * Children
  * Links To Other Web Sites
  * Social Media
  * Security
  * Other Terms and Conditions
  * Changes to Company’s Privacy Policy
  * Accessing Information; Contacting Company
  * Your California Privacy Rights
  * Information for Residents of the European Economic Area

#### Our Policy

Welcome to the website (the “Site”) of Ivisa.com by Document Advisor LLC (“Company”, “we”, “us” and/or “our”). This Site is operated by iVisa and has been created to provide information about our company, and to provide help, guidance, and the option to process online travel visas for any country (the “Company Services”) to our Site visitors (“you”, “your”). This Privacy Policy sets forth the Company’s policy with respect to information including personally identifiable data (“Personal Data”) and other information that is collected from Site visitors.

#### Information We Collect:

When you interact with us through the Site, we may collect Personal Data and other information from you, as further described below:

**Personal Data That You Provide Through the Site:**

  * We collect Personal Data from you when you voluntarily provide such information, such as when you contact us with inquiries, respond to one of our surveys, register for access to the Company Services or use certain Company Services like processing a travel visa. These data may be collected through our secure HTTPS forms or through any of our support channels (email, online chat or phone). The Personal Data we collect is the strictly necessary data to process a travel visa and may include the following: email, phone number, arrival date, port of arrival, reason for travel, home address, country of address, telephone number, name, last name, date of birth, city and country of birth, citizenship, gender, passport number, passport issue date, passport expiration date, passport place of issue, passport photo, passport information page scan, religion, family information (parents and spouses names, last names, place of birth, country of birth, and profession), professional details (occupation, employer name and address), address in destination . Wherever Company collects Personal Data we make an effort to provide a link to this Privacy Policy. By voluntarily providing us with Personal Data, you are consenting to our use of it in accordance with this Privacy Policy. If you provide Personal Data to this Site, you acknowledge and agree that such Personal Data may be transferred from your current location to the offices and servers of Company and the authorized third parties referred to herein located in the United States.

**Other Information:**

  * Non-Identifiable Data: When you interact with Company through the Site, we receive and store certain personally non-identifiable information. Such information, which is collected passively using various technologies, cannot presently be used to specifically identify you. Company may store such information itself or such information may be included in databases owned and maintained by Company affiliates, agents or service providers. This Site may use such information and pool it with other information to track, for example, the total number of visitors to our Site, the number of visitors to each page of our Site, and the domain names of our visitors' Internet service providers. It is important to note that no Personal Data is available or used in this process. 

  * Cookies: In operating this Site, we may use a technology called "cookies." A cookie is a piece of information that the computer that hosts our Site gives to your browser when you access the Site. Our cookies help provide additional functionality to the Site and help us analyze Site usage more accurately. For instance, our Site may set a cookie on your browser that allows you to access the Site without needing to remember and then enter a password more than once during a visit to the Site. In all cases in which we use cookies, we will not collect Personal Data except with your permission. On most web browsers, you will find a “help” section on the toolbar. Please refer to this section for information on how to receive notification when you are receiving a new cookie and how to turn cookies off. We recommend that you leave cookies turned on because they allow you to take advantage of some of the Site’s features. 

  * Aggregated Personal Data: In an ongoing effort to better understand and serve the users of the Company Services, Company often conducts research on its customer demographics, interests, and behavior based on the Personal Data and other information provided to us. This research may be compiled and analyzed on an aggregate basis, and Company may share this aggregate data with its affiliates, agents and business partners. This aggregate information does not identify you personally. Company may also disclose aggregated user statistics in order to describe our services to current and prospective business partners, and to other third parties for other lawful purposes.

#### Our Use of Your Personal Data and Other Information:

Company uses the Personal Data you provide in a manner that is consistent with this Privacy Policy. If you provide Personal Data for a certain reason, we may use the Personal Data in connection with the reason for which it was provided. For instance, if you contact us by email, we will use the Personal Data you provide to answer your question or resolve your problem. Also, if you provide Personal Data in order to obtain access to the Company Services, we will use your Personal Data to provide you with access to such services and to monitor your use of such services. Company and its subsidiaries and affiliates (the “Company Related Companies”) may also use your Personal Data and other personally non-identifiable information collected through the Site to help us improve the content and functionality of the Site, to better understand our users and to improve the Company Services. Company and its affiliates may use this information to understand personal travel patterns and contact you in the future to tell you about services we believe will be of interest to you. If we do so, each communication we send you will contain instructions permitting you to "opt-out" of receiving future communications. In addition, if at any time you wish not to receive any future communications or you wish to have your name deleted from our mailing lists, please contact us as indicated below.

If Company intends on using any Personal Data in any manner that is not consistent with this Privacy Policy, you will be informed of such anticipated use prior to or at the time at which the Personal Data is collected.

#### Our Disclosure of Your Personal Data and Other Information:

Company is not in the business of selling your information. We consider this information to be a vital part of our relationship with you. There are, however, certain circumstances in which we may share your Personal Data with certain third parties without further notice to you, as set forth below:

  * _Business Transfers:_ As we develop our business, we might sell or buy businesses or assets. In the event of a corporate sale, merger, reorganization, dissolution or similar event, Personal Data may be part of the transferred assets. 

  * _Related Companies:_ We may also share your Personal Data with our Related Companies for purposes consistent with this Privacy Policy.

  * _Agents, Consultants and Related Third Parties:_ Company, like many businesses, sometimes hires other companies to perform certain business-related functions. Examples of such functions include mailing information (FedEx or UPS), using visa agents to visit embassies, maintaining databases and processing payments. When we employ another company to perform a function of this nature, we only provide them with the information that they need to perform their specific function.

  * _Legal Requirements:_ Company may disclose your Personal Data if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to (i) comply with a legal obligation, (ii) protect and defend the rights or property of Company, (iii) act in urgent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of the Site or the public, or (iv) protect against legal liability.

  * _Partner Companies:_ We may also share your Personal Data with Partner Companies for purposes consistent with this Privacy Policy.

#### Your Choices:

You can use the Site without providing any Personal Data. If you choose not to provide any Personal Data, you may not be able to use certain Company Services, including but not limited to getting support, processing travel visas or retrieving existing information. In addition, you can stop receiving Company communications by opting out. Each communication we send you will contain instructions permitting you to "opt-out" of receiving future communications.

#### Online Advertising We Use:

We use Google AdWords and Google Adwords Remarketing to advertise our Company across the Internet. AdWords Remarketing will display relevant ads tailored to you based on what parts of the Ivisa.com website you have viewed by placing a cookie on your machine. THIS COOKIE DOES NOT IN ANYWAY IDENTIFY YOU OR GIVE ACCESS TO YOUR COMPUTER. The cookie is used to say "This person visited this page, so show them ads relating to that page." Google AdWords Remarketing allows us to tailor our marketing to better suit your needs and only display ads that are relevant to you.

How to Opt Out of Remarketing and Advertising If you do not wish to participate in our Google AdWords Remarketing, you can opt out by visiting Google's Ads Preferences Manager You can also opt out of any third-party vendor's use of cookies by visiting www.networkadvertising.org/choices/

#### Exclusions:

This Privacy Policy does not apply to any Personal Data collected by Company other than Personal Data collected through the Site. This Privacy Policy shall not apply to any unsolicited information you provide to Company through this Site or through any other means. This includes, but is not limited to, information posted to any public areas of the Site, such as blog posts (collectively, “Public Areas”), any ideas for new products or modifications to existing products, and other unsolicited submissions (collectively, “Unsolicited Information”). All Unsolicited Information shall be deemed to be non-confidential and Company shall be free to reproduce, use, disclose, and distribute such Unsolicited Information to others without limitation or attribution.

#### Children:

Company does not knowingly collect Personal Data from children under the age of 13. If you are under the age of 13, please do not submit any Personal Data through the Site. We encourage parents and legal guardians to monitor their children’s Internet usage and to help enforce our Privacy Policy by instructing their children never to provide Personal Data on this Site without their permission. If you have reason to believe that a child under the age of 13 has provided Personal Data to Company through this Site, please contact us, and we will endeavor to delete that information from our databases.

#### Links to Other Web Sites:

This Privacy Policy applies only to the Site. This Site may contain links to other web sites not operated or controlled by Company (the “Third Party Sites”). The policies and procedures we described here do not apply to the Third Party Sites. The links from this Site do not imply that Company endorses or has reviewed the Third Party Sites. We suggest contacting those sites directly for information on their privacy policies.

#### Social Media:

Through the Site, you can choose to access certain social media websites and services that are owned and/or controlled by third parties (including, without limitation, Facebook and Twitter) (such websites and services, collectively, the “Social Media Services”). When you elect to access and use the Social Media Services, you will be sharing your information (which will include personal information if you elect to share such information) with those Social Media Services. As with other Third Party Sites, the information that you share with the Social Media Services will be governed by the privacy policies and terms of service of the providers of such Social Media Services and not by the polices and procedures we describe here. You may also be able to modify your privacy settings with these Social Media Services to, for example, control what information the Social Media Services disclose to other entities, including Company. When you share our site with Social Media Services, we will collect relevant information necessary to enable the Site to access that Social Media Service, however you will provide your login information, like your password, directly to such Social Media Service (and not to Company). As part of such integration, the Social Media Service will provide Company with access to certain information that you have provided to such Social Media Service, and we will use, store and disclose such information in accordance with this Privacy Policy and, if and to the extent applicable, the policies of such Social Media Services. However, please remember that the manner in which Social Media Services use, store and disclose your information is governed by the policies of the applicable Social Media Services provider, and, as a result, Company shall not have any liability or responsibility for the privacy practices or other actions of Social Media Services that may be enabled within and/or otherwise accessible through the Site.

#### Security:

Company takes reasonable steps to protect the Personal Data provided via the Site from loss, misuse, and unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration, or destruction. However, no Internet or email transmission is ever fully secure or error free. In particular, email sent to or from this Site may not be secure. Therefore, you should take special care in deciding what information you send to us via email. Please keep this in mind when disclosing any Personal Data to Company via the Internet. Company provides a 24/7 phone line if you prefer to share sensitive data via phone.

#### Other Terms and Conditions:

Your access to and use of this Site is subject to the Terms of Use.

#### Changes to Company’s Privacy Policy:

The Site and our business may change from time to time. As a result, at times it may be necessary for Company to make changes to this Privacy Policy. Company reserves the right to update or modify this Privacy Policy at any time and from time to time without prior notice. Please review this policy periodically, and especially before you provide any Personal Data. This Privacy Policy was last updated on the date indicated above. Your continued use of the Site after any changes or revisions to this Privacy Policy shall indicate your agreement with the terms of such revised Privacy Policy.

#### Access to Information; Contacting Company:

To keep your Personal Data accurate, current, and complete, please contact us as specified below. We will take reasonable steps to update or correct Personal Data in our possession that you have previously submitted via this Site.

Please also feel free to contact us if you have any questions about Company’s Privacy Policy or the information practices of this Site.

You may contact us sending an email to [help@ivisa.com](mailto:help@ivisa.com).

#### Your California Privacy Rights:

Applicable California privacy legislation permits visitors who are California residents to request certain information regarding our disclosure of personal information to third parties for their direct marketing purposes. To make such a request to access such information, please contact us as follows: sending an email to [help@ivisa.com](mailto:help@ivisa.com). Within thirty (30) days of receiving such a request, we will provide a list of the categories of personal information disclosed to third parties for third-party direct marketing purposes during the immediately preceding calendar year, along with the names and addresses of these third parties. This request may be made no more than once per calendar year. We reserve our right not to respond to requests submitted other than to the address specified in this paragraph.

#### Information for Residents of the European Economic Area:

This section of the Privacy Policy applies only if you use our Site from a country in the European Union or another member state of the European Economic Area (“EEA”), and it supplements the information in the Privacy Policy.

iVisa is a data controller for processing of information defined as personal data under applicable data protection law (“Personal Data”) collected through our Site and by email, either directly from you or from travel agents acting on your behalf.

  * _LEGAL BASIS FOR DATA PROCESSING:_ We process Personal Data for the purposes set out in the Privacy Policy. Our legal bases to process Personal Data include processing that is necessary for the performance of a contract between us (for example, to provide you with services you request and to identify and authenticate you so you may use the website); necessary to comply with legal requirements and applicable accounting standards and to make mandatory disclosures to law enforcement and regulatory authorities; necessary for our legitimate interests (for example, to manage our relationship with you, to improve the website and our services, to protect our property and safeguard against fraud and malware, to make or defend legal claims); and based on consent by our customers (for example, to communicate with you about our products and services and provide you with marketing information). Where we process your Personal Data with your consent, you may subsequently withdraw consent at any time by contacting us (using the contact instructions below), without affecting the lawfulness of processing based on consent before its withdrawal.

  * _EU DATA SUBJECT RIGHTS:_ The EU General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR) and other applicable data protection laws provide certain rights for individual data subjects (“EU Data Subject Rights”). You may decline to share certain Personal Data with us, in which case we may not be able to provide some of the features and functionality of our services. These rights include, in accordance with applicable law, the rights to access or rectify Personal Data, object to or restrict further processing, or request the erasure of Personal Data or, where feasible, to have it moved to a new service provider (“data portability”). Requests should be submitted by contacting us using the contact instructions below. You may access and change certain Personal Data by logging into our website and updating the account settings page and other features. Otherwise, we will make commercially reasonable efforts to provide you reasonable access to your Personal Data within 30 days of your access request to the contact address below. We provide this access so that you may review, make corrections, or request deletion of your Personal Data. If we cannot honor your request within 30 days, we will inform you when we will be able to provide such access. If for some reason access is denied, we will provide an explanation. When technically feasible, at your request, we will provide your Personal Data to you or transmit it directly to another controller. We retain your Personal Data while you have an account with us and while you are using our services or continuing to visit our website. We will retain your Personal Data for as long as it is reasonably necessary for the purposes set out in the Privacy Policy, considering the time period reasonably necessary to: provide the services to you, exercise the choices and rights you have requested, comply with our contractual obligations, enforce our terms for use of the services, and comply with legal and regulatory requirements. If you have any unresolved privacy concern that we have not addressed satisfactorily after contacting us, you have the right to contact the relevant national data protection supervisory authority and lodge a complaint

  * _CONTACT US:_ For all EU Data Subject Rights requests, you must put the statement "Your EU Data Subject Rights" in the subject field of your request and include in the request the name of the Services with respect to which you are requesting the information, as well as your contact information. If you have questions or wish to exercise EU Data Subject rights, please contact us at [help@ivisa.com](mailto:help@ivisa.com). Our EU representative is Sergio Merino, located in Calle Antonia Merce 8, 28009, Madrid, Spain.
